insubuy.com 2019-06-20

# Insubuy Privacy Policy

At Insubuy, Inc., we are committed to protecting the privacy of visitors of our websites. This notice describes how and why we collect, use and disclose your personal information when you interact with Insubuy. 

This privacy notice covers www.insubuy.com, [www.brokersnexus.com](https://brokersnexus.com/) and other websites available to visitors throughout the world. These websites are operated in the United States in accordance with laws of the United States, which may differ from those of your residence country. 

###  Cookies 

"Cookies" are used on our web sites. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site your computer when you visit our web sites. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you. 

There are certain cookies that are strictly necessary such as Google Tag Manager and Session Information which are necessary for the interaction with our websites. We use performance tracking and interaction cookies such as Google Analytics and Google Translate. We also use targeting and advertising cookies such as Google AdWords, DoubleClick, Bing Ads, Facebook Pixel. 

You have the right to accept or decline cookies through your browser preferences. However, if you decline cookies, many features of the web site may not be available to you. 

###  Collection of Personal Information 

We collect various types of information in order to operate efficiently and provide you the most suitable products and services. In order to get insurance quotes, it is necessary for you to provide the coverage dates, ages, geographic information, coverage desired and similar non-personally identifiable information. However, in order to purchase the insurance, you would need to provide personal information including name, gender, citizenship, home country, birth date, address, phone number, email address, passport number or other government issued ID number, payment details including card information, beneficiary details. 

Just like most websites, we gather certain information automatically such as IP address, browser type, International Service Provider (ISP), referring/exist pages, the webpages viewed, operating system, date/time stamp to analyze the trends in the aggregate and administer the web sites. 

Our web sites have discussion forums, and question and answer sections where the user can post any content. Please keep in mind that any information you publicly share on the internet is visible by anyone. 

###  Security of Personal Information 

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of generally accepted standards of security technologies and procedures to help protect the personal information submitted to us, from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, both during transmission and once it is received. Information on our website is transmitted through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. However, we cannot guarantee our ability as internet transmission is not 100% secure. The personal information stored on our computer systems is in controlled facilities in a secure building in the United States and has limited access. 

If you are required to enter the User ID and password to access any part of our web sites, it is your responsibility to secure your password and not share with anyone. Do not save your password when accessing our web sites when using a shared computer. 

###  Use of Your Personal Information 

Any personal information we collect about you or from you by web site, phone, email, fax or in person is kept strictly confidential. Our staff has access to your personal information strictly on a need to know basis and to provide the services to you. 

We will retain your personal information subject to its retention schedules, which are determined by the nature of the personal information, how we will use the information to serve you, any regulatory control and any applicable legal or tax considerations. 

###  Sharing of Your Personal Information 

We generally do not disclose, sell or rent your personal information to any third parties, other than to the insurance companies or their plan administrators who are required to have it in order to provide products and services to you. 

In certain cases, we are required by law to disclose information to law enforcement, or in case of lawsuit or subpoena or other legal process. Personal data may be tranferred to a third party if there is a transfer of assets or ownership of Insubuy or if Insubuy files for bankruptcy. 

###  Tracking, Advertisement and Marketing 

Our web sites use Google Analytics. That includes obtaining specific visitor cookie data, such as the source, medium and keyword use to visit our web sites. However, Google Analytics does not store any visitor specific data but only aggregate data. Insubuy has implemented and uses Google Analytics for Display Advertisers and Google Display Network. Google Analytics collects anonymous data about your interaction with our website and through the standard Google Analytics implementation. Anonymous data may be used for purposes including delivering to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites and selecting offers and products to display to you when you visit our website. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can find out more about how Google uses cookies in advertising and opt-out via the following links: [Google Display Network](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) and [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

We may use personal data to display custom, personalized content to our web site visitors and send newsletters, emails, promotional material and other updates to our users. You can at any time opt out of it by unsubscribing. 

###  General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 

Unless stated otherwise, where and when GDPR applies to the data collected on our web sites, Insubuy is the data controller. If you are a citizen or resident of the European Union (EU) or Switzerland, and you are visiting our websites or are insured through us, your personal data will be sent outside the EU to the United States for use and processing as necessary to provide products and service to you. In such cases, your personal information will be transferred subject to the EU-U.S. & Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. 

You hereby, consent to process your personal information pursuant to Article 6(1)(a) of the GDPR by accepting our privacy policy. You may withdraw your consent at any time. 

For insureds, customers and website visitors, we will: (i) process the personal information we collect from you or that we receive from third parties about you as necessary to further our legitimate interests, which shall not override any of your fundamental rights and freedoms; (ii) process such information in order to send you future marketing materials about products or services in which you may have interest; and (iii) for all other purposes set forth here. 

###  Accessing Your Personal Information 

If you are EU or Swiss individual, upon request, we will provide you with the information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by logging into your account or contacting us. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. In certain circumstances we may be required by law to retain your personal information or may need to retain your personal information in order to continue providing you a service. 

Contact Information for Insubuy's Data Protection Officer: 

Insubuy, Inc.  
4200 Mapleshade Ln Ste 200  
Plano, TX 75093  
Phone: +1 (866) INSUBUY  
Email: [opd](mailto:opd)

Your right to access your personal data may be restricted in exceptional circumstances, including, but not limited to, when the burden or expense of providing this access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy in the case in question, or when the rights of persons other than you would be violated by the provision of such access. If we determine that your access should be restricted in a particular instance, we will provide you with an explanation of our determination and respond to any inquiries you may have. 

###  EU-US & Swiss-US Privacy Shield 

Insubuy, Inc. committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on each Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework's applicable Principles. To this end, Insubuy, Inc. complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland transferred to the United States pursuant to Privacy Shield. Insubuy, Inc. adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to such data. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and data subject rights under the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/ 

###  Children 

Our websites are not intended for use by children under the age of 13 years. Accordingly, we do not solicit or knowingly collect any personal information from anyone who visits our websites that we know to be under 13 years age. Parents and/or guardians are solely responsible for supervising their minor children's use of our web sites. If we are made aware that information is or has been submitted by or collected from a child under 13 years of age, we will take reasonable steps to delete their personal information. However, this provision does not apply for insureds whom we provide services as a result of a customer or an insured relationship. 

###  Third Party Privacy Practices 

Our privacy policy does not address, nor are we responsible for the privacy policies of any third parties to which Insubuy links or submits insurance enrollment information to. We are not responsible for nor have control over the privacy policies other organizations such as insurance companies, plan administrators, social media companies (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram etc.) or technology companies (Google, Apple, Microsoft etc.), including any personal information you disclose to other organizations through online quotes, purchase or in connection with our social media pages. 

###  Changes 

We may need to update our privacy policy from time to time without prior notice to user. However, in that case, updated privacy policy will be posted here. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. 

Last Updated: May 15, 2019
